{
    "facilityDetails": [
        "Upper floors accessible by elevator",
        "Toilet paper",
        "Child safety socket covers",
        "Bidet",
        "Hardwood or parquet floors",
        "Linen",
        "Electric kettle",
        "Slippers",
        "Clothes rack",
        "Kitchenware",
        "Dining area",
        "Heating",
        "Dining table",
        "Refrigerator",
        "Bath or shower",
        "Kitchenette",
        "Single-room air conditioning for guest accommodation",
        "Streaming service (like Netflix)",
        "Detached",
        "Free toiletries",
        "Desk",
        "Kitchen",
        "Toilet",
        "TV",
        "iPod dock",
        "Tile/marble floor",
        "Hairdryer",
        "Socket near the bed",
        "Microwave",
        "Private entrance",
        "Towels"
    ],
    "question_answer": [
        {
            "question": "Is there an elevator for guests?",
            "answer": "Yes, we have an elevator which go from basement to the top floor of the building."
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you have a room with three single beds? Is there elevator?",
            "answer": "Our \"Standard Triple Room\" has 3 beds (1,2m). And yes we have elevator."
        },
        {
            "question": "Hi, do you have cooking facilities for group of 20?",
            "answer": "Hello, we don't have a place to cook for many people"
        },
        {
            "question": "Does the Double Room have air conditioning?",
            "answer": "No, our room temperature always from 20-23 degree whole year so we don't need AC. Only the rooftop room (Deluxe Studio) have AC system because it hot up there. "
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you have secure car parking available?",
            "answer": "I'm sorry. We only have parking for motorbikes"
        },
        {
            "question": "We intend to book a superior studio for 2 of us and 2 kids, age 1 and 4.\nDo you provide a portable heater or can you help us rent a portable heater for our room.",
            "answer": "Hello, we can rent a portable heater for you or there are another option that the smaller room: Deluxe Studio with King-size bed, which have an AC system so you don't need a heater if you choose this room."
        },
        {
            "question": "do you have washing facilities or is there a laundry close by? Thank you",
            "answer": "There is a laundry shop near by, just 5 minutes of walking. We also have washing facilities but it will more expensive."
        },
        {
            "question": "Hello, for the Quadruple room, there is a total of 4 beds, right? Since there is 2 bunk beds",
            "answer": "As you can see in the photo of the room, the quadruple room have only 2 double beds for 4 peoples. (1,6m lower bed and 1,4m upper bed)"
        },
        {
            "question": "How is the payment handled? Through Booking.com or direct to the host?",
            "answer": "Hello, our guests will pay at the property, not through Booking.com, and not prepaid. "
        },
        {
            "question": "Is there air conditioning in Superior Studio? (60 sq.metre room)",
            "answer": "Sorry, we don't have air conditioning in Superior Studio. Only the Deluxe King Studio has an AC."
        }
    ]
}
